  {
    quizId: "buoys",
    quizName: "Buoys and Channel Markers",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "Safe Water",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1599707367072-cd6ada2bc375?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "Isolated Danger",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1500382017468-9049fed747ef?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "New Danger",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1532187643603-ba119ca4109e?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "Port",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1532187863486-abf9dbad1b69?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "Starboard",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1519003722824-194d4455a60c?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
	        {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "North",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1599707367072-cd6ada2bc375?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "East",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1500382017468-9049fed747ef?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "South",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1532187643603-ba119ca4109e?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "West",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1532187863486-abf9dbad1b69?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      },
      {
        question: "What does this indicate?",
        answer: "Do Not Pass",
        image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1519003722824-194d4455a60c?w=600&auto=format&fit=crop"
      }
    ]
  }